怎么回事，森林惹到你了？
So what happened? Did a forest tick you off?
我们一直说需要一个放信件的地方
We always say we need a place for the mail.
所以我就动工了，然后呢 我决定更上一层楼
I started building one. But then I decided to take it to the next step.
你要盖邮局？
You're building a post office?
不是，是一个娱乐专用柜 内含信件柜
No,an entertainment unit,with a built-in mail cubby.
顶多一天就能搞定 好
It's a one-day job,max.
天呐，还真贴身啊
My word,those are snug!
这是我的旧工作裤
These are my old work pants.
“塞尔吉奥瓦伦特”
Sergio Valente.
刚才电锯有点失控
Power saw kind of got away from me there.
本集播出：小弗兰克
The One With Frank Jr.
菲比，你弟出现了吗？
Hey,Pheebs. Any sign of your brother?
还没，不过他很爱迟到
No,but he's always late.
你不是只见过他一次？ 是啊
-I thought you only met him once. -I did.
这样讲很像姐姐的样子 “弗兰克老是迟到”
I think it sounds big sister-y,"Frank's always late."
别急，他会来的
Well,relax. He'll be here.
我知道，我只是很紧张
I know. I'm just nervous.
我妈死了，我不和我姐说话
It's just,Mom's dead,don't talk to my sister...
外婆最近都在睡觉
...Grandma's been sleeping a lot lately.
这是我拥有家人的最后机会
It's just the "last-desperate- chance-to-have-a-family" kind of thing.
你真好，还陪我等
You're sweet to wait with me.
事实上，是甘瑟叫我来的 杯子不能拿出来
Actually,Gunther sent me. You're not allowed to have cups out here.
还有谁觉得大卫科波菲尔（魔术大师）可爱？
Does anyone else think David Copperfield's cute?
没有，不过他告诉我 他觉得你是个迷人的时髦女郎
No. But he told me he thinks you're a fox.
珍妮丝喜欢他
All right. Janice likes him.
事实上，她非常喜欢他 把他放进她的“免费赠品”名单里
In fact,she likes him so much,she put him on her "freebie" list.
她的什么？
Her what?
我们说好 一人可以挑五个名人上床
We have a deal where we each pick five celebrities we could sleep with...
另一个人不准生气
...and the other one can't get mad.
每一对儿健康男女关系的中心是：
The heart of every healthy relationship:
诚实、尊重、与名人上床
Honesty,respect and sex with celebrities.
你的名单有谁？
So who's on your list?
金贝辛格（名模、影星）
IKim Basinger...
辛迪克劳馥（名模）、哈利贝瑞（黑人女星）
... Cindy Crawford,Halle Berry...
杰丝敏布丽丝（《海滩游侠》中的角色）
...Yasmine Bleeth...
和兔子杰西卡（著名卡通兔子明星）
...and Jessica Rabbit.
你知道她是卡通人物 而且和你不是一个物种吧？
You do realize that she is a cartoon,and way out of your league?
我知道，我是看看 我能不能让她的眼珠弹出来
I know. I just wonder if I could get her eyes to pop out of her head.
如果我当初也有这么一个名单的话，安妮也不会甩了我
Annie Esposito would never have dumped me had we had a list like this.
还有，当然了，如果她妹妹是名人的话
And also, of course,if her sister was famous.
莫妮卡，你会选谁？
Who would yours be?
我得先交男朋友，才能列名单
First,I need a boyfriend. Then I can have a list.
只是个游戏，莫
It's just a game,Mon.
瑞秋，你呢？
Rach,how about you?
不晓得，应该是克里斯奥唐纳（《蝙蝠侠与罗宾》） 小约翰F肯尼迪（前总统肯尼迪的儿子）
I don't know. I guess Chris O'Donnell,John F.Kennedy Jr...
丹尼尔戴路易斯（《我的左脚》）、史汀（摇滚歌手） 和帕克斯蒂文森（《硬汉》）
... Daniel Day-Lewis,Sting and Parker Stevenson.
《蜘蛛侠》？（是彼得帕克主演）
Spiderman?
《硬汉》
Hardy Boy.
是彼得帕克 谢谢
-Peter Parker. -Thank you.
你呢？你会选谁？
What about you,honey? Who'd be on your list?
这种事需要深思熟虑
That kind of thing requires some serious thought.
我会先把可能人选分门别类
First,I'd divide my prospective candidates into categories.
怪人
What a geek!
各位，这是弗兰克 我同父异母的弟弟
Everybody,this is Frank! My half brother,Frank!
就是他们
This is everybody.
这是罗斯 你好吗？
-This is Ross. -How are you?
钱德 乔伊
Chandler，Joey
这是莫妮卡
This is Monica.
这是瑞秋
And this is Rachel.
我去点咖啡
I'm gonna get coffee for us.
你们男人怎么有心思做得了事？
Hey,how do you guys get anything done?
我们是没做什么事
We don't,really.
你们有什么计划吗？
Do you guys have big plans?
有，我们要好好的联络感情
Oh,yeah. We're gonna connect and bond and everything.
我们会去时代广场 买几个忍者明星
I thought we could go down to Times Square and pick up some ninja stars.
我朋友赖瑞托我拍妓女的照片
My friend,Larry,he wants me to take a picture of a hooker.
我们都没有充分利用住在这里的优势
We really don't take advantage of living in the city.
抱歉，我钻到你了？
Oh,sorry. Did I get you?
没有，你没有钻到我
No,you didn't "get" me!
那是电钻
It's an electric drill!
你要是钻到我，我就死了
You "get" me,you kill me!
别激动 你要不要这个柜子嘛？
Calm down! Do you want this unit or not?
我不要这个柜子
I do not want this unit!
你应该早告诉我的，我又不会读心术
You should've told me before. I'm not a mind reader.
没有啤酒了，我要去莫妮卡那边
And we're out of beer. I'm going to Monica's.
很好
Fine!
你穿这样要去哪里？ 1982年？
Where you heading in those pants? 1982?
对了，我在装潢建材店 看到名牌瓷砖在特价
I saw down at the hardware store,they got those designer tiles on sale...
你可以重铺浴室地板
...if you wanna redo your bathroom floor.
我的浴室地板怎么了？
What's wrong with my bathroom floor?
没什么，只是又旧又暗
Nothing. It's just old and dingy,that's all.
没有这回事
I highly doubt that.
你把筐移开…
If you move your hamper...
就能看到瓷砖原来的颜色
...you see how the tile used to be.
这样我怎么住！怎么办？
I can't live like this! What are we gonna do?
别激动，拿着
Relax. Here,hold this.
瓷砖一撬就掉，我弄给你看
This old stuff comes right up. I'll show you.
我没想到你要撬它
A little more than I wanted to see.
你看看，黏得多死啊
Look at that! Every inch of this is glued down!
撬也撬不完，我看你别管了
It'd take forever to pry this up. You should just leave it.
怎么能不管 你在我的旧地板上撬了个洞
I can't leave it! You gouged a hole in my dingy floor!
这样就好了
There. There you go.
挺好的
Yeah,that's nice.
等外科医生把这个从你的结肠取出来之后就可以放回原位了
We can put it back there after the surgeons remove it from your colon!
还我一个新地板
Give me a new floor!
不行，我要是完不成那个柜子钱德会杀了我
l can't. Chandler will kill me if l don't finish the unit.
-我会付你双倍于他给你的价格 -他没给我钱
-l'll pay you double what he's paying you.-He's not paying me anything.
三倍
Triple.
什么？  我知道我要问什么了 你会卷舌头吗？
What? I know what I wanted to ask you. Can you roll your tongue?
因为我会，但是我妈不会
Because I can and my mom couldn't.
我想那一定是爸的遗传
And I figured that was something I got from our dad.
等一下，你是说这样？
Well,wait,you mean like this?
对，你也会
Yeah,you can do it too. Yeah.
你没有卷啊
You're not doing it.
好吧 所以是我妈会，我不会
Oh,right. Okay. Yeah,my mom could and I can't.
我们这一点不一样
We don't have that.
你的生日是哪一天？
When's your birthday?
2月16日
February 16th.
我认识一个18日的人
I know a guy who's the 18th.
蛮近的
That's close.
你的生日呢？
When's yours?
10月25日
October 25th.
跟万圣节同一个月
That's the same month as Halloween.
你在家里喜欢做什么？
So what kind of things do you like to do at home?
熔化东西
Melt stuff.
好，我已经挑了三个 三个什么？
-Okay,I've got three of my five. -Three of your five what?
可以上床的名人
Celebrities I'm allowed to sleep with.
天哪，你还真慎重
God,you're giving this a lot of thought.
很难挑好吗？我只剩两个空缺
Hey,it's hard,okay? I only have two spots left.
你筛选出谁了？
All right. Who you got it narrowed down to?
伊丽莎白赫莉（性感明星）
Elizabeth Hurley.
很迷人
Very attractive.
心胸宽大
Forgiving.
苏珊莎兰登（演技派明星）
Susan Sarandon.
她太热衷政治了
You know what? She's too political.
她可能会叫你先捐四个罐头
She'd probably make you donate four cans of food first.
还有伊莎贝拉罗塞里尼（影星英格丽褒曼的女儿，久居欧洲）
And lsabella Rossellini.
很辣、很性感
Very hot. Very sexy.
但是太国际化了 她不会跑来美国的
But she's too international. She's never gonna be around.
所以呢？ 所以你得掌握胜算
-So? -So you gotta play the odds.
挑一个会一直在国内的人
Pick somebody who's gonna be in the country all the time.
对啊，你之所以得不到她 是地理因素
Yeah. Because that's why you won't get lsabella Rossellini. Geography.
你说的“熔化”就是熔化啊
Okay. So by "melting" you meant melting.
这是艺术吗？
So is it,like,art?
要熔化艺术也可以
Yeah,you can melt art.
可以借个电话吗？
Hey,can I use your phone?
当然，你要打给你妈？ 不是，我想拿来熔化
-Sure. You want to call your mom? -No,I want to melt it.
只溶化数字键，这样电话还能用
Just the numbers.lt will still work.
现在不行
Oh. Well,not right now.
我要去睡了，烟熏得我头痛
I'm gonna go to bed. The fumes are giving me a headache. So....
晚安，老弟
Good night,"bro."
晚安
Good night.
拿去
Here.
以防万一
Just in case.
太好了
Oh,excellent!
那是什么空手道？ 什么都不是
-What kind of karate is that? -No kind.
那是他自创的
He just makes it up.
你们处得怎样？ 目前为止还是蛮烂的
-How's it going with you guys? -So far it kind of blows.
我以为他会更有兄弟的感觉
I don't know,I just thought he'd feel more like a brother.
就像你和罗斯，亲密融洽
Like you and Ross. Close and connected and....
现在是很亲，但是以前
We're close now. You wouldn't believe the years...
我们又吵又打，又拉又扯
...of noogies,and wedgies,and flying wedgies,and atomic wedgies and....
然后裙子就会被扯到头上来
That's when the waistband goes over your head.
我们还玩影子游戏让对方发狂
We drove each other crazy playing the shadow game.
什么是影子游戏？ 什么是影子游戏？
-How do you play the shadow game? -How do you play the shadow game?
我在问你啊 我在问你啊
-I just asked you. -I just asked you.
我没空跟你闹
I don't have time for this.
这就是影子游戏 你放弃得真快
-That is what the game is. -You just gave up really quickly.
有看到乔伊吗？ 怎么了？
-Seen Joey? -What's the matter?
就是这个
Oh,just this!
其实是我不好 沙发就是用来放亮光漆的
It's my fault,really,because the couch is where we keep the varnish.
有没有人把瓷砖拿给我
Somebody wanna hand me one of those tiles?
怎么回事？ 他在帮我重铺地板
-What's going on? -He's retiling my floor.
泥水匠
Spackle boy!
给我起来 你要有始有终
-Get up! -You started this,you'll finish it!
是我先受害的
He started mine first!
辛德瑞拉（灰姑娘），去做柜子 辛德瑞拉，去铺瓷砖
Build the unit,Cinderellie Lay the tile,Cinderellie
-他先帮我弄的 -不，我需要浴室，我是女生
-He was helping me first.-No, l need a bathroom. l'm a girl!
你们自己商量，我先休息一会儿
You guys figure it out.l'm taking a break.
-很好 -休息一会儿？
-That's good.-Take a break?
是的，我认为就算是上帝也会在第七天休息一下（《圣经》创世纪）
Yeah. l think even God rested on the seventh day.
乔伊，如果这个需要花七天…
Joey, if this takes seven days...
你会去见上帝，然后自己问他关于这个的事情
...you'll be able to meet God and ask him about it yourself.
大章鱼
Big octopus.
天哪，我都忘了
Oh,my God! I totally forgot!
不能找别人吗？
Well,can't someone else do it?
但是我有客人
But I have company.
没关系，我去
Look,that's all right. I'll come in.
对不起，我得去工作
I'm sorry,but I have to go into work.
我的一个熟客坚持要让我做
It's one of my regulars who's insisting that I do him,so....
你在做什么工作？
Hey,what kind of work do you do?
我是按摩师
I'm a masseuse.
我帮客人按摩
I give people massages and stuff.
你在按摩院工作？
You work at one of those massage parlors?
我们不那样叫，不过没错
Well,you know,we don't call it that. But,yeah.
好劲爆
That's wild.
我完全不知道
No,I had no idea.
好吧
Alrighty.
我过一会儿就回来
I'll be back in a little bit.
除非你想跟我去
Unless you want to come with me.
你是说去看吗？
You mean,like,watch?
不是，你也可以接受服务 而且是免费招待
No. No,you can get one yourself. It'll be on the house.
不然要姐姐干什么？
What are big sisters for?
我并不想这个…，你知道的
Well,I don't think this. You know?
不…我不会亲自招呼你
No. No,no. I wouldn't do you myself.
那样很奇怪
I mean,that would be weird.
我会请其他小姐来为你做
I'll get one of the other girls to do it.
真好玩
This is so much fun!
你兴奋吗？ 是的
Are you excited?
莫妮卡和瑞秋 也在那里工作吗？
Hey,do Monica and Rachel work there?
好漂亮
It's beautiful!
就跟之前地板的样子一样
It's like the first bathroom floor there ever was!
你想进去干什么？
What are you going in there for?
你想一起吗？
You want,like,a number?
再见
Hi. Bye.
好，我选好了
Okay. I'm done with my choices.
这是最后名单
These are final.
你也该选好了 对啊，好正式
-Well,it's about time. -Yeah. Very official.
对，这是钱德用他的电脑打印的
Oh,yeah. Well,you know,Chandler printed it up on his computer.
谁拿去压膜的？
And who laminated it?
是我
That was me.
拿来我看看
All right,let me see.
乌玛瑟曼（《杀死比尔》）、薇诺娜瑞德（《纯真年代》） 伊莉莎白赫莉
"Uma Thurman,Winona Ryder,Elizabeth Hurley...
米歇尔法伊弗（《纯真年代》）
... Michelle Pfeiffer...
多萝西哈米尔？（滑冰名将）
... Dorothy Hamill"?
这是我的名单
Hey,it's my list!
你知道她只有在冰上 才会一直转吧？
You do realize she only spins like that on ice?
怎么了？ 她扭断了我的手
-What's going on? -She broke my arm!
他摸我的屁股 是她先摸我的
-He touched my fanny. -She touched mine first!
那是我的工作
That's my job!
什么意思？ 我可以跟你做爱，却不能摸你？
So what's the deal? I can have sex with you but I can't touch you?
你不能跟她做爱 你以为我是妓女？
-You can't have sex with her! -Did you think I was a hooker?
不，我知道你是按摩师 冷静点，我又不是警察
No,okay. I know. You're a masseuse. It's cool. I'm not a cop!
你去请威佛先生等5分钟
Ask Mr. Wiffler if he can wait for five minutes.
好
Fine.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
你以为我是干那行的？天哪！
So that's what you thought I did? God!
我不是干那行的
That's not what I do!
你不是干那行的？
Wait,that's not what you do?
不是
No!
你怎么会这么想？
Why would you think that?
不知道，这是城里嘛
I don't know. This is the city,you know? I just....
我是说…
I mean...
我不知道
... I don't know.
随便，好一个完美的周末 完美的句点
Whatever. It's the perfect end to the perfect weekend anyway.
等一下
Oh,wait.
你说得没错，真的很完美
No,you're right. No,it was perfect.
我居然把它搞砸了
I can't believe I screwed it up so bad.
你觉得很完美？
You thought it was perfect?
也许称不上完美
Well,no,maybe it wasn't perfect...
但还是很酷
... but you know,it was pretty cool,you know?
我们聊得那么愉快
Because we had all those great talks,you know?
你觉得哪一次特别愉快？
Which ones in particular were great for you?
就是卷舌头的事
Well,you know,about the tongue thing,you know?
还有我告诉你 我喜欢什么，讨厌什么
And how I told you about my likes and my dislikes.
我喜欢熔化东西 不喜欢不能熔化的东西
How I like to melt stuff,and how I dislike stuff that doesn't melt.
对，好
Right. Okay.
我有话都能对你说 因为你是我姐姐
I feel like I can really talk to you because you're my sister,you know?
是啊，大概吧
Yeah. I guess I do.
结果我却摸你朋友 惹你生气
And then I go feel your friend up and make you mad at me.
我也没有气得跳起来
Well,I wasn't hopping mad,you know?
你有跳一、两下
You hopped a little bit.
我真的很抱歉
Yeah,I'm really sorry. You know,I'm really....
算了
Okay.
我觉得现在这一刻最棒了
Well,this is my favorite part of the weekend. Right now. This.
现在？
This?
拜托，我们去了时代广场
Oh,come on. We went to Times Square.
买到忍者明星 我差点被妓女扭断手
We found ninja stars. I almost get my arm broken by a hooker
她不是妓女
She's not a hooker.
我跟朋友吹嘘时，她就是
When I tell my friends about her,she will be.
菲比，那是什么
Phoebe, what's that?
小弗兰克临走前给我的，一件礼物
Frank Jr. gave me this before he left.A present.
以前是属于我爸的，他开车库门用的
lt used to belong to our dad.His garage-door opener.
直到弗兰克熔化了它
Until Frank melted it.
酷
Cool!
铃声响起，集合所有能找到的人
Sound the bell, gather up all the men you can find.
我们自己要把娱乐柜举起来
We got ourselves an entertainment unit raising.
不 说真的，你们能帮我们吗
No, seriously,can you help us?
数到三
On 3!
一、二…
1,2
为什么不数到二？
Why don't we just go on 2?
为什么？
Why 2?
这样比较快
Because it's faster.
如果没有关于“二”的对话，我都已经数到三 四遍了
I could've counted to 3 four times without all the "2" talk.
好，但是以后… 这个柜子很重，不会变轻的！
-All right,but in the future -Heavy thing! Not getting lighter!
一、二…
1,2
所以要数到二吗？
So we are going with two?
乔伊，干得好
A good job,Joe.
哇
Wow.
好大
It's big.
是很大，显得我们的门看起来小了
So big it actually makes our doors look smaller.
可能是量尺有问题
Maybe my ruler's wrong.
可能所有的量尺都有问题
Maybe all the rulers are wrong.
还好嘛，你的挡一点点 我的挡一点点
It's not that bad. So it blocks a little of your door,a little of mine.
我有更好的主意
I got a better idea.
干脆不要挡我的，都去挡你的
How about it blocks none of my door,and a lot of your door?
听着，趁着我还记得，那边油漆未干
Listen,before I forget,that side is still wet.
衣服上的毛粘住了…
Arm hair stuck!
我跟你确认一下
Let me just see if I've got this right.
是咖啡因减半、中大杯 少许榛果
So this is a half-caf,double-tall,easy hazelnut...
脱脂牛奶、不要奶泡、要打过 要非常烫的拿铁，对吧？
... nonfat,no foam,with whip,extra-hot latte,right?
太好了
Okay. Great.
变态
You freak.
伊莎贝拉罗塞里尼
Isabella Rossellini
谢谢
Thank you.
一杯咖啡外带
A coffee to go,please.
是伊莎贝拉罗塞里尼！
Isabella Rossellini!
不会吧？天哪！
Are you serious? Oh,my God!
该死！我居然把她从我的名单删掉
Damn! I cannot believe I took her off my list!
怎么？不然你会行动吗？
Why? Because otherwise you'd go for it?
也许
Yeah,maybe.
骗人
You lie.
你不认为我会行动？
You don't think I'd go up to her?
你花了十年承认你喜欢我
It took you 10 years to finally admit you liked me.
是吗？小姑娘，你最好庆幸 这份名单已经压膜了
Yeah? Well,missy,you better be glad that list is laminated.
这样吧，你过去 就当她是候补人选
You know what,honey? You go ahead. We'll call her an alternate.
好，帮我拿油煎饼
Hold my cruller.
你真的要让他去？
Are you really gonna let him do this?
亲爱的，他要去泡伊莎贝拉罗塞里尼耶
He's about to go hit on lsabella Rossellini.
可惜没有爆米花可吃
I'm just sorry we don't got popcorn.
你好，我是罗斯
I'm Ross.
你不认识我 但我是你的超级影迷
You don't know me,but I'm a big,big fan of yours.
我是说…
I mean...
《蓝丝绒》（一部粗俗血腥暴力性乱的争议电影）
...Blue Velvet.
我能不能请你喝一杯咖啡？
I was wondering if I could maybe buy you a cup of coffee.
或是把钱还给你
Or reimburse you for that one.
你不是跟那个女生一对儿？
Aren't you with that girl over there?
算是啦
Well,yeah,kind of.
但是没关系，我们相互理解
But that's okay. We have an understanding.
我们都有一份五个名人的名单 你就在我的名单上
We each have this list of five famous people,and you were one of mine.
所以她允许我可以跟你上床
So I'm allowed to sleep with you.
这是恭维
It's flattering.
还是算了
I don't know
等一下嘛，伊莎贝拉
Wait. Wait,lsabella.
先别急着否决 这可是千载难逢的机会
Don't dismiss this so fast. This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
对你而言
Yeah,for you.
这就是名单？
Is that the list?
我可以看吗？
-Yes. -Can I see it?
看一下嘛 好吧
-Come on. -But Okay.
我不在名单上
I'm not on the list!
这不是定稿
But that's not the final draft.
都压膜了
It's laminated.
对，好吧，你本来在名单上
Okay,see,you were on my list.
但是我的朋友钱德…
But then my friend,Chandler...
指出你太国际化了
... brought up the point that you are international.
所以我拿薇诺娜瑞德 取代你，本国的
So I bumped you for Winona Ryder. Local.
真是太讽刺了 因为我也有一份名单
You know,it's ironic,because I have a list...
列了五个咖啡店蠢人
...of five goofy coffeehouse guys.
就在昨天，那个人取代了你
And yesterday,I just bumped you for that guy over there.
我们当朋友就好了
We're just gonna be friends.
你知道吗？
You know what?
我赌我塞得进去
Bet you I could fit in there.
我拿5元赌你塞不进去
I got five bucks says you can't.
掏支票吧，先生
Get out your checkbook,mister.
我有现金
Oh,I think I have the cash.
你这个失败者，老兄
You are dog,man!
我塞得刚刚好
I totally fit!
是啊，被你赢了
Yeah. You got me.
我输了5元大钞
I'm out five big ones.
拿去吧
There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
赢了
Cha-ching!
林肯先生，你好（纸币上有林肯的头像）
Oh,well,hello,Mr. Lincoln!
祝你下次好运，伙计
Better luck next time,buddy!
酒钱由我出
And the drinks are on me!